It's easy to customize your notes.

Make your notes stand out and get noticed.

• Format text using different fonts and font sizes
• Add emphasis with bold and italic text styles or color.
• Include graphics . 
￼
Stickies has lots of other great features, including a spell checker, import and export features, and other ways to arrange and customize your notes. Plus, you'll find a "Make New Sticky Note" service in many applications.

Look in Help to find out more about using Stickies.